<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zhaokai</title>
    <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/authors/zhaokai/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/authors/zhaokai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Zhaokai</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright Zhaokai AllRightsReserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/images/icon_hu48ea973b72a836bf9a5fd0201387e78c_21303_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Zhaokai</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/authors/zhaokai/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narva course 2024 </title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/post/narvacourse2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/post/narvacourse2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Please refer to the original version to our group blog &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/blogs/emd/&#34;&gt;KTH EMD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As some of you already knew that I finally made up my mind to take a position in the academia rather than in the industry, it’s always hard for me to explain why. I’m neither a enthusiastic speaker nor a percipient thinker. It can be challengeable for me to go towards a position in a university. I thought that I should have lost my mind at that time. It drives me to explore my internal desire for this decision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before that, let me say some good word for our group, from the perspective of a native Chinese PhD. I have to admit that I’m so lucky to work in the EMD group, which “pulls” me to develop my research area in the postdoc period. (Footnote: the reason why I used “pull” rather than “push” is that I need to be efficient and open-minded dealing with my project work while exploring more research area freely. I don’t feel pushed or stressed out, and receive lots of help and supports. “push” is a negative word rather than a neutral word in my language). My supervisor Luca gave me the freedom to investigate the challenge and difficulty in the industry so that it could show the direction of our future work. In other words, I could work closely with Zparq and ABB to gain more experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, it’s Luca who decided to join this project/team (ExpSkills-REM), whose latese event was to give the course at Narva. The aim of ExpSkills-REM is to educate professionals who work or intend to work in the field of permanent magnets along the whole value chain, including recycling and motor applications: Raw Materials, Technological Magnets, Circular Economy and Electromobility coming together. In Narva Estonia, Neo Performance Materials is building a permanent magnet factory, making it the first of its kind in Europe and the Western world. I hope this magnet product will be used in the permanent magnet motor soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this course, thanks to the help and support of Luca, I had enough time to prepare our one-day module “Design and fabrication of REM-based devices and components” for this four-day course. Everything goes on well on those days except the heavy snow in Narva when we were visiting the factory.
&lt;img src=&#34;./featured.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Snowy day&#34; title=&#34;Snowy day&#34;&gt;
Then, it became sunny again in the nex day.
&lt;img src=&#34;./featured2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sunny day&#34; title=&#34;Sunny day again&#34;&gt;
For me, it’s the first time to give the course for the whole day. It is definitely a milestone in my life, but really tiring. Hence, I took a wonderful sauna after the course. There were always lots of interesting and useful discussion about some contents of the course, which inspired the teachers as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming back to the first question in this post, when comparing academia with industry, one of the major difference is that the position of the academia requires the duty of teaching and supervision, which is as important as the researching. I then realized that it’s also a great joy for me to discuss about the technical detail in the project as well as the philosophy of life. I hope to support my future friends (namely students) to freely explore their research and lifestyle. I already have been lucky enough to get this privilege at KTH and ZJU and I hope in the near future I also have the ability to share this luck/opportunity to those who believe in this way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As this is my last weekend at KTH, I would like to say Hej då to all of you, EMD noblemen, project colleagues, and EPE friends. Take good care of yourself, as it is merely the deadline of the course, project, or paper, not the end of the world. Keep in touch and see you again.
&lt;img src=&#34;./featured3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Bye&#34; title=&#34;Bye&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Hej då! KTH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/20230324/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/20230324/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m really happy to have seven month research stay at ABB Corporate Research Center in Västerås, Sweden. ABB colleagues are nice and friendly. I wish to have more contact with them both for work and spare time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/20230401/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/20230401/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was really happy to be one of the team member. The knowledge of permanent magnet is useful for the motor designer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scalable Analytical Model for Calculating the Magnetic Field of Surface-Mounted Permanent Magnet Motor</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/the-scalable-analytical-model-for-calculating-the-magnetic-field-of-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/the-scalable-analytical-model-for-calculating-the-magnetic-field-of-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stockholm Bonfire</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/post/newyear2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/post/newyear2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m really happy to spend the first day of 2024 with my beloved wife and my best friends.
(This post also help me to learn how to put a video in the blog, hahaha)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Happy New Year!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video controls preload=&#34;auto&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34;  playsinline class=&#34;html-video&#34;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&#34;https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/post/newyear2024/bofire.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos, but don&#39;t worry, you can &lt;a href=&#34;https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/post/newyear2024/bofire.mp4&#34;&gt;download it&lt;/a&gt; and watch it with your favorite video player!&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiment</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/20231230/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/20231230/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m really happy to learn from it!
&lt;strong&gt;Happy New Year!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal Paper</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/20231224/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 01:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/20231224/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I would appreciate all the co-authers for their contribution in the paper entitled &amp;ldquo;Hybrid Analytical Model of Permanent Magnet Linear Motor Considering Iron Saturation and End Effect&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal Paper</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/23-tie-1322/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 01:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/news/23-tie-1322/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I would appreciate all the co-authers for their contribution in the paper entitled &amp;ldquo;The Scalable Analytical Model for Calculating the Magnetic Field of Surface Mounted Permanent Magnet Motor&amp;rdquo;. This paper entitled was submitted to IEEE Transactions on Industrial Electronics on 21-Apr-2023， revised on 09-Aug-2023 and 15-Nov-2023, accepted on 31-Jan-2024.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study at IEMDC 2023 </title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/post/iemdc2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/post/iemdc2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Please refer to the original version to our group blog &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/blogs/emd/&#34;&gt;KTH EMD&lt;/a&gt;.
It has been half a year since I participated in this international conference. Before I start to memorize the event at that conference, I would like to recommend some good conferences that are related to our research field (Maybe useful for fresh PhD and master students).  ECCE and ICEM are two of the most famous conferences in the field of electrical machines, I think. ECCE is held every year, while ICEM is held every two years. Besides, I would recommend ICEMS, PEMD, and IEMDC which attract lots of motor engineers. For the motor design, Intermag and CEFC are good conferences, where many conference papers can be published in the IEEE Transaction on Magnetics. Meanwhile, IECON is related to the field of motor control. As the transportation electrification is more and more popular nowadays, I think we can consider submitting the papers to VPPC and ITEC.&lt;br&gt;
Let’s come back to the conference IEMDC 2023. Please allow me to copy the description of this conference from the official &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.iemdc.org/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; so that I don’t need to summarizeit :). The 14th IEEE International Electric Machines and Drives Conference (IEMDC) was held May 15-18, 2023 in San Francisco, CA. IEMDC provides a forum to share technology advances and new developments in the design, operation, analysis, and applications of electric machines and drives. Contributions are invited from industry, academia, and other sectors. Accepted and presented papers will be published in the Conference Proceedings, which will be submitted to the IEEE Xplore® digital library. Papers presented at IEMDC may be submitted to IEEE Transactions on Industry Applications, IEEE Transactions on Energy Conversion, IEEE Transactions on Industrial Electronics, or IEEE Transactions on Power Electronics, according to the rules specific to each journal.&lt;br&gt;
This year, I guessed that only two hundred participants, which is not as large as before. For me, I found two interesting trends from the tutorial of the conference. The first interesting topic is the application of hairpin winding. Still, lots of researchers are working on the improvement of the hairpin winding. The professors from the University of Nottingham gave excellent speeches to show their findings. The other interesting topic is the application of additive manufacturing (3-D print) on motor design. The Marquette University built a high power density motor equipped with additively manufactured windings and integrated with advanced cooling and modular integrated power electronics, which is fascinating. Of course, other tutorial topics are very interesting, but I cannot join as they were held at the same time slot.&lt;br&gt;
At the conference, I met lots of famous professors from all over the world and engineers from well-known companies. I felt that we needed to know more about the accomplishments that the company has already achieved and try to fulfill the needs of the industry if we could (or we can focus). That will be beneficial to both academia and industry. &lt;br&gt;
Last but the least, I would like to present our papers at this conference entitled ”Design Comparison of Outer- and Inner-Rotor Permanent Magnet Motors for Hydrofoil Boat”. It gives some comparison of different kinds of PM motors. I hope to extend this paper soon and submit it to the journals. &lt;br&gt;
Finally, I would like to present some beautiful pictures of San Francisco. I love the weather there. Even though I was told that it was dangerous in the city center, I felt safe during my stay. Some pictures around the city.&lt;br&gt;
By the way, I’m looking forward to seeing the post of IECON 2023, in which I was absent. I believe that Yixuan, Gustaf, and Xinpo had a pleasant time in Singapore. It is really nice to see that EMDers reunite somewhere. I cannot say that I didn’t envy you guys. Also, I hope to see you all soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Merry Christmas!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Robust Deadbeat Predictive Current Control Method for IPMSM</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/a-robust-deadbeat-predictive-current-control-method-for-ipmsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/a-robust-deadbeat-predictive-current-control-method-for-ipmsm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Improved Rotor Position Estimation Method for SPMSM with Misaligned Hall-Effect Sensor</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/an-improved-rotor-position-estimation-method-for-spmsm-with-misaligned-hall-effect-sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/an-improved-rotor-position-estimation-method-for-spmsm-with-misaligned-hall-effect-sensor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Analytical Model for Predicting the Electromagnetic Losses in Surface-Mounted Permanent-Magnet Motors</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/hybrid-analytical-model-for-predicting-the-electromagnetic-losses-in-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/hybrid-analytical-model-for-predicting-the-electromagnetic-losses-in-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nonlinear Analytical Model-Embedded Optimal Design for ER-PMSM</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/nonlinear-analytical-model-embedded-optimal-design-for-er-pmsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/nonlinear-analytical-model-embedded-optimal-design-for-er-pmsm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analytical Analysis of Quasi-Halbach Array Permanent-Magnet Motors Based on Field Separation Theory</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/analytical-analysis-of-quasi-halbach-array-permanent-magnet-motors-based-on-field-separation-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/analytical-analysis-of-quasi-halbach-array-permanent-magnet-motors-based-on-field-separation-theory/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reliability-Oriented Multi-Objective Optimization of Electrical Machines Considering Insulation Thermal Lifetime Prediction</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/reliability-oriented-multi-objective-optimization-of-electrical-machines-considering-insulation-thermal-lifetime-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/reliability-oriented-multi-objective-optimization-of-electrical-machines-considering-insulation-thermal-lifetime-prediction/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Comparison of Outer- and Inner-Rotor Permanent Magnet Motors for Hydrofoil Boat</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/conference-design-comparison-of-outer-and-inner-rotor-permanent-magnet-motors-for-hydrofoil-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/conference-design-comparison-of-outer-and-inner-rotor-permanent-magnet-motors-for-hydrofoil-boat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo Academic&amp;rsquo;s Markdown slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplementary notes can be added here, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34;&gt;code and math&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Natural Position Observer with Vertical Detection Coil for FSCW Machines</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/a-natural-position-observer-with-vertical-detection-coil-for-fscw-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/a-natural-position-observer-with-vertical-detection-coil-for-fscw-machines/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analytical Model of Electromagnetic Performance for Permanent-Magnet Vernier Machines Using Nonlinear Exact Conformal Model</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/analytical-model-of-electromagnetic-performance-for-permanent-magnet-vernier-machines-using-nonlinear-exact-conformal-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/analytical-model-of-electromagnetic-performance-for-permanent-magnet-vernier-machines-using-nonlinear-exact-conformal-model/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Identification of Inductance and Flux Linkage for Inverter-Fed SPMSMs Using Switching State Functions</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/online-identification-of-inductance-and-flux-linkage-for-inverter-fed-spmsms-using-switching-state-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/online-identification-of-inductance-and-flux-linkage-for-inverter-fed-spmsms-using-switching-state-functions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overall Electrical Parameters Identification for IPMSMs Using Current Derivative to Avoid Rank Deficiency</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/overall-electrical-parameters-identification-for-ipmsms-using-current-derivative-to-avoid-rank-deficiency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/overall-electrical-parameters-identification-for-ipmsms-using-current-derivative-to-avoid-rank-deficiency/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigation of Analytical Models for Surface-Mounted Permanent Magnet Motor Using Voltage Source Inverter</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/investigation-of-analytical-models-for-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motor-using-voltage-source-inverter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/investigation-of-analytical-models-for-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motor-using-voltage-source-inverter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analytical Calculation of Eccentric Surface-Mounted Permanent-Magnet Motor Accounting for Iron Saturation</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/analytical-calculation-of-eccentric-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motor-accounting-for-iron-saturation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/analytical-calculation-of-eccentric-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motor-accounting-for-iron-saturation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nonlinear Analytical Model for Predicting Magnet Loss in Surface-Mounted Permanent-Magnet Motors</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/nonlinear-analytical-model-for-predicting-magnet-loss-in-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/nonlinear-analytical-model-for-predicting-magnet-loss-in-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nonlinear Analytical Modelling for Surface-Mounted Permanent Magnet Motors with Magnet Defect Fault</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/nonlinear-analytical-modelling-for-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motors-with-magnet-defect-fault/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/nonlinear-analytical-modelling-for-surface-mounted-permanent-magnet-motors-with-magnet-defect-fault/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electromagnetic Analysis for Interior Permanent-Magnet Machine Using Hybrid Subdomain Model</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/electromagnetic-analysis-for-interior-permanent-magnet-machine-using-hybrid-subdomain-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/electromagnetic-analysis-for-interior-permanent-magnet-machine-using-hybrid-subdomain-model/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Parameter Estimation for Permanent Magnet Synchronous Motors</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/full-parameter-estimation-for-permanent-magnet-synchronous-motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/full-parameter-estimation-for-permanent-magnet-synchronous-motors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Consideration of Fractional Slot Concentrated Winding Interior Permanent Magnet Synchronous Motor for EV and HEV Applications</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/design-consideration-of-fractional-slot-concentrated-winding-interior-permanent-magnet-synchronous-motor-for-ev-and-hev-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/design-consideration-of-fractional-slot-concentrated-winding-interior-permanent-magnet-synchronous-motor-for-ev-and-hev-applications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nonlinear Analytical Analysis of External Rotor Permanent-Magnet Synchronous Motor</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/nonlinear-analytical-analysis-of-external-rotor-permanent-magnet-synchronous-motor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/nonlinear-analytical-analysis-of-external-rotor-permanent-magnet-synchronous-motor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Improved Hybrid Field Model for Calculating On-Load Performance of Interior Permanent-Magnet Motors</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/an-improved-hybrid-field-model-for-calculating-on-load-performance-of-interior-permanent-magnet-motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/an-improved-hybrid-field-model-for-calculating-on-load-performance-of-interior-permanent-magnet-motors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Modified Deadbeat Predictive Current Control for Improving Dynamic Performance of PMSM</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/a-modified-deadbeat-predictive-current-control-for-improving-dynamic-performance-of-pmsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/a-modified-deadbeat-predictive-current-control-for-improving-dynamic-performance-of-pmsm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open-Circuit Field Prediction of Interior Permanent-Magnet Motor Using Hybrid Field Model Accounting for Saturation</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/open-circuit-field-prediction-of-interior-permanent-magnet-motor-using-hybrid-field-model-accounting-for-saturation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/open-circuit-field-prediction-of-interior-permanent-magnet-motor-using-hybrid-field-model-accounting-for-saturation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rotating Permanent Magnets Based Flux Pump for HTS No-Insulation Coil</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/rotating-permanent-magnets-based-flux-pump-for-hts-no-insulation-coil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/rotating-permanent-magnets-based-flux-pump-for-hts-no-insulation-coil/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On-Load Field Prediction of Surface-Mounted PM Machines Considering Nonlinearity Based on Hybrid Field Model</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/on-load-field-prediction-of-surface-mounted-pm-machines-considering-nonlinearity-based-on-hybrid-field-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/on-load-field-prediction-of-surface-mounted-pm-machines-considering-nonlinearity-based-on-hybrid-field-model/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design and Testing of an Impact Sensor Using Two Crossed Polyvinylidene Fluoride (PVDF) Films</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/design-and-testing-of-an-impact-sensor-using-two-crossed-polyvinylidene-fluoride-pvdf-films/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/design-and-testing-of-an-impact-sensor-using-two-crossed-polyvinylidene-fluoride-pvdf-films/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hybrid Field Model for Open-Circuit Field Prediction in Surface-Mounted PM Machines Considering Saturation</title>
      <link>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/a-hybrid-field-model-for-open-circuit-field-prediction-in-surface-mounted-pm-machines-considering-saturation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhaokai-ee.github.io/publication/a-hybrid-field-model-for-open-circuit-field-prediction-in-surface-mounted-pm-machines-considering-saturation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
